instaprints.com 2013-09-27

# Instaprints - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Effective January 1, 2012

About Instaprints.com

Instaprints is an online marketplace for buying and selling Instagram photos as framed prints, canvas prints, greeting cards, and other "print on demand" products.

Information Collected from Members

After opening an account with Instaprints, members are able to create detailed on-line profiles, including: the member's name, biography, artwork, phone number, e-mail address, and more.  All of this information is fully disclosed on the Instaprints.com website.  Any site visitor that visits Instaprints.com and navigates to the member's "profile page" will be able to view all of the profile information that has been entered by that member.

Use of Cookies

Instaprints.com uses cookies to store the city, state, and zipcode of all visitors to the website.  Instaprints.com is a location-based website.  Visitors that view the site from Chicago are able to view a custom site that is dedicated to Chicago and the surround area.  Similarly, a visitor from New York City will view a different site which is dedicated to New York City and the surrounding area.  To enhance the visitor's browsing experience, we store a cookie on the visitors computer which will allow us to remember the visitor's location next time they return to the site.

We do not link the cookie to any personally identifiable information that visitors may submit while on the website.

Links

Instaprints.com contains links to other websites.  Instaprints.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites.  When linking to another site, a visitor should read the privacy policy stated on that site.  Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Instaprints.com.

Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time, Instaprints.com may make changes to our privacy policy.  If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users and providers aware of what the changes are so that they will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it.   A member is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.  If, however, we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify by posting a notice on our website for thirty days. 

Contacting Instaprints.com

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@instaprints.com.
